<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jasmine Anand</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jasmine Anand</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I decided to work with two Marvel datasets because I am a huge Marvel fan. I have watched all the Marvel movies at least 3 times and have also read a lot of the Marvel comic books. Through this projct I wanted to see if I can find any associations through the datasets I have chosen. For this Project, I will be analyzing 2 different Marvel datasets. The first dataset, called stats, has information on abilities of each of the Marvel Characters, such as intelligence, strength, power, and speed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction For this project, I will be using the Titanic dataset. I am interested to see if I can see some relationship between survivial rate and other factors such as class, gender, and age.  This dataset has 14 variables. The variable pclass states the passenger class, which can be 1,2, or 3. The variable sibsp is the number of siblings/spouses the person on board and the variable parch is the number of parents/children on board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
